<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dragana Radanovic&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dragana Radanovic&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 13:47:08 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://draganaradanovic.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to discover new interesting graphic novels?</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/how-to-discover-new-interesting-graphic-novels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/how-to-discover-new-interesting-graphic-novels/</guid>
      <description>Last week you asked how I find interesting new comics to read. Hmm, I am a professional comic book reader, as I like to say. What does it mean? I read comics even if I find them unappealing on the first ball, and also if by my personal taste they are in the basket labelled “Naah”.
But this wasn’t always like that. I think it all started when I was really young.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make a short comic story?</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/how-to-make-a-short-comic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/how-to-make-a-short-comic/</guid>
      <description>SHORT COMIC STORY, the comic form that many believe it is hardest to make. There is a limited amount of pages (you can&amp;rsquo;t fit an action movie into 1-4 pages, or you can?).
Last week I was determined to make a short story, but as soon as I started thinking about the topic of the story, I gave up. If I couldn&amp;rsquo;t decide about the topic I want to draw, how could I come up with the story?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview for Pulp DeLuxe</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/pulp_deluxe_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/pulp_deluxe_interview/</guid>
      <description>http://www.pulpdeluxe.be/verhoor-dragana-radanovic/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUCA Show 2019</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/luca-show-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/luca-show-2019/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimental Comic Laboratory</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/001_pfc_student_edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/001_pfc_student_edition/</guid>
      <description>From January 16 to 23, the EESI joined FIBD and the ChiFouMi association to host the international Pierre Feuille Ciseaux workshop, led by Nicolas Verstappen, author and teacher at Chulalongkorn University, Bangkok. It is a laboratory residence around experimental comics, which has been created and conducted many times in France and the United States. This year, 20 students from 10 international schools were invited to participate in this residency, in parallel with the residency which brings together professional authors, the same week and a few kilometres from Angoulême.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am an artist with completed Bachelor studies in Animation and visual effects and Master studies in Graphic storytelling, especially interested in children’s literature regarding difficult topics, unconventional children’s books and graphic narratives about marginalized experiences of the world. Currently living in Leuven, Belgium.
Artist in residency Experimental comics residency-laboratory (PFC#6 : ChiFouMi des étudiants)
Angouleme, France, January 2019.
ReLocation
residency, Destelheide Hanenbos, Belgium, June 2018.
Exhibitions Exibited comic pages from “Socks lost in war”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stay in touch</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>