<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dragana Radanovic&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dragana Radanovic&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 13:47:08 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://draganaradanovic.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to discover new interesting graphic novels?</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/how-to-discover-new-interesting-graphic-novels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/how-to-discover-new-interesting-graphic-novels/</guid>
      <description>Last week you asked how I find interesting new comics to read. Hmm, I am a professional comic book reader, as I like to say. What does that mean? I read comics even if I find them unappealing at first sight, and also if by my personal taste they belong to the basket labelled “Naah”.
But this wasn’t always like that. I think it all started when I was really young.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make a short comic story?</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/how-to-make-a-short-comic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/how-to-make-a-short-comic/</guid>
      <description>SHORT COMIC STORY, the comic form that many believe it is hardest to make. There is a limited amount of pages (you can&amp;rsquo;t fit an action movie into 1-4 pages, or you can?).
Last week I was determined to make a short story, but as soon as I started thinking about the topic of the story, I gave up. If I couldn&amp;rsquo;t decide about the topic I want to draw, how could I come up with the story?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUCA Show 2019</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/luca-show-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/luca-show-2019/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimental Comic Laboratory</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/001_pfc_student_edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/post/001_pfc_student_edition/</guid>
      <description>From January 16 to 23, the EESI joined FIBD and the ChiFouMi association to host the international Pierre Feuille Ciseaux workshop, led by Nicolas Verstappen, author and teacher at Chulalongkorn University, Bangkok. It is a laboratory residence around experimental comics, which has been created and conducted many times in France and the United States. This year, 20 students from 10 international schools were invited to participate in this residency, in parallel with the residency which brings together professional authors, the same week and a few kilometres from Angoulême.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/research/</guid>
      <description>REDRAWING CHILDHOOD PhD in the Arts  --
Although since the very beginning comics were strongly connected to children, scholars argue that children&amp;rsquo;s literature represents the adult author&amp;rsquo;s nostalgic memories of their own childhood rather than truthful depictions of it.--  &amp;ldquo;REDRAWING CHILDHOOD&amp;rdquo; challenges the conventions of using formal aspects of graphic narratives in reconstructing representations of childhood and finding new ways of storytelling regarding that life period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BIO</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/about/</guid>
      <description>-- Ever since I painted all room&amp;rsquo;s walls with the crayons, when I was 5 years old, nothing could stop me from painting the world in my colours. I got grounded, of course, but I also got tons of paper so that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t use the wall as my canvas again. That&amp;rsquo;s how my journey started! As expected, I completed Bachelor studies in Animation and visual effects. Right after I started working for the regional TV station, in the unit for PR and Promotion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STAY IN TOUCH</title>
      <link>https://draganaradanovic.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://draganaradanovic.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>WORK INQUIRIES EMAIL: didadragana@gmail.com
I will be happy to hear from you! Please note that I may not answer during the weekends, but I will be back to you shortly. Thanks for your patience!
WORKING TOGETHER Have a project that I could help you with? I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to hear about it!
Not sure which information can help me understand the project better? Write what kind of work needs to be done, what is it for, when is the deadline and your budget if possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>